<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GreedyCoder</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="bookmarks">Saved Problems</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="setting">Setting</string>

    <string name="theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="dark_mode">Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="light_mode">Light Mode</string>
    <string name="system_default">System Default</string>
    <string name="choose_a_theme">Choose a theme</string>

    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="clear_data">Clear Data</string>

    <string name="error_disk_full">Oops, it seems like your disk is full.</string>
    <string name="error_unknown">Oops, something went wrong.</string>
    <string name="error_request_timeout">The request timed out.</string>
    <string name="error_no_internet">Couldn't reach server, please check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="error_too_many_requests">Your quota seems to be exceeded.</string>
    <string name="error_serialization">Couldn't parse data.</string>
    <string name="error_not_found">Not Found!</string>
    <string name="invalid_image">Invalid image</string>

    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="clear_data_title">Confirm Deletion</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">Disclaimer: ReadOut is an open-source application designed to provide book summaries and audiobook playback functionality. It fetches book data using the Open Library API, generates summaries via the Google Gemini API, and converts these summaries into audio using the Google Cloud Text-to-Speech API. The app and its content are provided for informational and educational purposes only and are not a substitute for the original books or professional advice. While every effort has been made to ensure the accuracy and reliability of the app, it is provided "as is" without any warranties, express or implied. Users are encouraged to verify the original book content and comply with copyright laws when using the app. The developers and contributors are not liable for any errors, inaccuracies, or issues resulting from third-party APIs or data sources. By using [Your App Name], you agree to these terms and acknowledge that all usage is at your own risk. For further inquiries, please contact tawhidmonowar@gmail.com or visit https://github.com/tawhidmonowar/ReadOut.</string>
    <string name="clear_data_warning">Are you sure you want to delete all saved data? This action cannot be undone, and you will permanently lose all saved information.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text_audio_book">Disclaimer: This application integrates third-party APIs to provide users with a rich and versatile experience. The LibriVox API is used to fetch audiobooks, offering access to a vast collection of public domain recordings. The Gemini API is employed to generate concise and insightful summaries of text content, enhancing accessibility and understanding. Additionally, the Google Cloud Text-to-Speech API is utilized to convert text into high-quality, natural-sounding speech for an enhanced auditory experience. While we strive to ensure that the content and services offered through these APIs are accurate, reliable, and up-to-date, we cannot guarantee the completeness or error-free nature of the information provided. All data and functionality depend on third-party services, which are subject to their own terms of service and privacy policies. By using this application, you agree that the developers and providers of this app are not responsible for any errors, omissions, or inconsistencies in the content or any issues arising from the use of third-party APIs. For detailed information about these services, please refer to the official documentation or websites of the respective API providers.</string>
    <string name="about_app">ReadOut is a cross-platform app for Android and Desktop, built with Kotlin Multiplatform. It seamlessly integrates book discovery, audiobook playback, and AI-powered summaries in both text and audio formats. Discover new books, enjoy a diverse library of audiobooks, and access concise, insightful summaries — all designed to save your time and keep you informed.</string>
    <string name="search_result">Search Result</string>
    <string name="no_search_result">No Results Found</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go Back</string>
    <string name="right_arrow">Right Arrow</string>

</resources>